{
    "subject": "resource/Tapulous",
    "predicate": "ontology/industry",
    "object": "resource/Video_game",
    "human_readable": "Tapulous is an industry related to Video game.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8814073204994202,
            "question": "What industry is Tapulous related to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8413753509521484,
            "question": "Are there popular games associated with Tapulous?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.683659017086029,
            "question": "What are some examples of popular games within the Tapulous industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6000667810440063,
            "question": "Are there companies or individuals specializing in Tapulous?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5603659152984619,
            "question": "Can Tapulous involve creating new game mechanics?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5181565284729004,
            "question": "How has technology influenced the Tapulous industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4316551387310028,
            "question": "Tapulous likely involves what type of activity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42465442419052124,
            "question": "Is Tapulous a growing or declining industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35670551657676697,
            "question": "What types of skills might be needed to work in the Tapulous industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.33037638664245605,
            "question": "Could Tapulous involve the use of a touchscreen?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tapulous is an industry related to Video game.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4815_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What types of skills might be needed to work in the Tapulous industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4815_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Tapulous a growing or declining industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4815_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tapulous likely involves what type of activity?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4815_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4815_106.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4815_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4815_146.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4815_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4815_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4815_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4815_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4815_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4815_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4815_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because the documents provided contain information that confirms Tapulous as a video game developer and publisher, specifically mentioning their popular iPhone and iPad video game series, the Tap Tap series."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide extensive information about Tapulous as a video game developer, including details about its games and the acquisition by Walt Disney. This strongly supports the statement that Tapulous is related to the video game industry."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}